I have a gun.
I could come by tomorrow.
You're so funny, Arthur.
Yeah.
You know, I do stand-up comedy.
You should maybe
come see a show sometime.
I could do that.
Yeah?
Yeah. You'll let me know when?
Yeah.
If you're happy
and you know it
wiggle your ears
if you're happy
and you know it
wiggle your ears
if you're happy and you know it
and you really want to show it
wiggle your ears
if you're happy and you know it
stomp your feet
and you really want to show it
if you're happy and you know it
stomp your feet
shout "hurray"
if you're happy and you know it
and you really want to
hoyt, please, I love this job.
Arthur, I need to know why
you brought a gun
into a kids' hospital.
It's a prop.
It's part of my act now.
That's bullshit. Bullshit.
What kind of clown
carries a fucking gun?
Besides, Randall told me
you tried to buy a .38
off him last week.
Randall told you that?
You're a fuck-up, Arthur,
and a liar.
You're fired!
Jefferson street.
Next stop, ninth ave.
I'm telling you,
she wanted my number.
We should've just stayed.
You're dreaming, man.
She wasn't interested at all.
Are you nuts? Did you
see how close we were dancing?
She was in love.
She couldn't wait to
get away from you.
Ryan! Ryan, am I crazy?
Tell him what you saw.
Hey,
you want some French fries?
Hello?
Talking to you. Hey.
No, thank you.
You sure?
They're real good.
Don't ignore him.
He's being nice to you.
Whoo...
Is something funny, asshole?
Bitch!
Isn't it rich?
Are we a pair?
Me here at last on the ground
and you in mid-air
send in the clowns
isn't it bliss?
Don't you approve?
One who keeps tearing around
and one who can't move
where are the clowns?
There ought to be clowns
So, buddy, tell us,
what's so fucking funny?
Nothing.
I have... I have a condition.
I'll tell you what you have,
you asshole.
Whoa!
Please, stop!
We got a kicker, huh?
Hey, hold him steady.
Hold him steady.
Stay down, freak!
Hey!
Ninth Avenue.
Next stop, hunter's point.
Hey!
Stand clear of
the closing doors.
Shit. Shit.
I read it was
a guy in full makeup.
No, it says right here
it was a mask.
Either way, I think
it's good for business.
They got clowns on the front
of every newspaper.
Big man, what's the good word?
Hey.
Hey, Arthur,
I heard what happened.
Sorry, mate.
Yeah.
It doesn't seem fair,
getting fired like that.
Did you really bring a gun
to the children's hospital,
Artie?
What the fuck
would you do that for?
Is that part of
your new act, Arthur?
If your dancing
doesn't do the trick,
you're just gonna
shoot yourself?
Why don't you
ask Randall about it?
It was his gun.
- What?
- I still owe you for that,
don't I?
What the fuck
are you talking about?
Stop talking
out of your ass, art.
Oh, no!
I forgot to punch out.
And turns to sorrow
king of all hear me call
hear my name carnival
And as our city
tries to make sense
of the brutal triple murder
on the subway last week,
we're joined by Thomas Wayne.
Happy, look,
Thomas Wayne's on TV.
Yes, mother.
Thanks for
having me on, Chuck.
They're asking him about
those horrible subway murders.
Thank you, Thomas.
I know
this is a difficult time
for you.
Why him?
Looks like he's gained weight.
Yes, all three worked
for Wayne investments.
Good, decent, educated.
Although I didn't know
any of them personally.
Like all Wayne employees,
past and present,
they're family.
Did you hear that?
I told you, we're family.
There now seems to be
a groundswell of anti-rich
sentiment in the city.
It's almost as if
our less fortunate residents
are taking the side
of the killer.
Yes, and it's a shame.
It's one of the reasons why
I'm considering a run for mayor.
Gotham's lost its way.
What about the eyewitness report
of the suspect being
a man in a clown mask?
Well,
it makes total sense to me.
What kind of coward would do
something that cold-blooded?
Someone who hides behind a mask.
Someone who is envious
of those more fortunate
than themselves,
yet they're too scared
to show their own face.
And until those kind of people
change for the better,
those of us who have
made something of our lives
will always look
at those who haven't
as nothing but clowns.
Thomas Wayne, thank you
for coming in this morning.
It's not funny.
I heard this song on the radio
the other day,
and the guy was singing
that his name was carnival.
Arthur...
Which is crazy,
because that's
my clown name at work.
And until a little while ago,
it was like nobody ever saw me.
Even I didn't know
if I really existed.
Arthur, I have
some bad news for you.
You don't listen, do you?
I don't think
you ever really hear me.
You just ask
the same questions every week.
"How's your job? Are you
having any negative thoughts?"
All I have are
negative thoughts,
but you don't listen anyway.
I said, for my whole life,
I didn't know
if I even really existed.
But I do.
And people are
starting to notice.
They've cut our funding.
We're closing down
our offices next week.
The city has cut funding
across the board.
Social services is part of that.
This is the last time
we'll be meeting.
Okay.
They don't give a shit
about people like you, Arthur.
And they really
don't give a shit
about people like me, either.
Fuck.
How am I supposed to
get my medication now?
Who do I talk to?
I'm sorry, Arthur.
I think... I think most women
look at sex like buying a car.
You know, like, "can I see
myself in this long-term?"
"Is it safe?"
"Is it reliable?"
"Could it kill me?"
Most guys, we look at sex
like parking a car.
We're like, "there's a spot."
"There's another spot.
"That would work."
"Oh, I have to pay?
Never mind."
"Handicapped?
I hope no one sees this."
All right, that's my time.
Thank you very much, guys.
One more time
for Sam morril, y'all.
All right, now,
this next comic describes
himself as
a lifelong Gotham resident
who from a young age
was always told
that his purpose in life
was to bring laughter and joy
into this cold, dark world.
Um... okay.
Please help me welcome
Arthur fleck, y'all.
Arthur fleck.
Hello, it's good to be here.
I hated school when I was a kid.
I hated school as a kid.
My mother would say,
"you should enjoy it.
One day, you'll have to
work for a living."
"No, I won't, ma,
I'm gonna be a comedian."
Um...
Here's one.
You know, I was
just thinking the other day,
why are the rich people...
Smile though your heart is aching
smile even though it's breaking
when there are clouds in the sky
you'll get by
if you smile
through your fear and sorrow
smile and maybe tomorrow
you'll see the sun
come shining through for you
you believe that shit?
Fuck 'em.
I think the guy
that did it is a hero.
Three less pricks
in Gotham city,
only a million more to go.
You'll get by
that's the time you must keep on trying
smile, what's the use of crying
you'll find that
life is still worthwhile
if you just smile
And, buddy, as always,
thanks for the laughs.
I'm sure we'll see you again.
You know we'll be here, right?
I hope.
Tomorrow night, we have
Diana Hudson, Greg Gordon,
and animal expert, Hugh little.
Thanks for watching.
Good night, and always remember,
that's life.
That's life.
Momma, time to wake up
and go to bed.
Hmm? Oh...
Oh, happy.
Happy, I wrote a new letter.
Come on, dance with me.
For Thomas Wayne.
It's important.
You smell like Cologne.
It's 'cause
I just had a big date.
Oh.
Just don't forget to mail it.
The Murray Franklin
show is taped live
before a studio audience
in beautiful downtown
Gotham city.
You're gonna kill me. You're
gonna give me a heart attack!
Don't give me your...
No. No.
I'm not talking to you
until you stop being angry!
Okay.
I'm not angry, mom.
I'm not angry.
Please.
Mom, is this real?
He's an extraordinary man,
happy.
He's a very powerful man.
We were in love.
He said it was best that
we not be together
because of appearances.
And I could never
tell anyone because...
Well, I signed some papers.
And besides, you can imagine
what people would say
about Thomas and me.
What they'd say about you.
What would they say, mom?
Hmm.
Hi.
What's your name?
I'm Bruce.
Bruce.
I'm Arthur.
That's better.
Bruce! Bruce!
Get away from that man.
It's okay. I'm a good guy.
What are you doing?
Who are you?
I'm here to see Mr. Wayne.
Well, you shouldn't be
speaking to his son.
Why did you give him
these flowers?
No, they're not real.
It's magic.
I was just trying to
make him smile.
Well, it's not funny, is it?
Do I need to call the police?
No. Please.
My mother's name is penny.
Penny fleck.
She used to work here years ago.
Can you please tell Mr. Wayne
I need to see him?
You are her son.
Yeah.
Did you know her?
I know about the two of them.
She told me everything.
There's nothing to know.
There is no "them."
Your mother was delusional.
She was a sick woman.
Don't say that.
Just go.
Mmm?
Before you
make a fool of yourself.
Thomas Wayne is my father.
He left me.
Let go! Let go!
Keep the respirations above 15.
Slow and steady.
We got some stairs coming up.
Mom?
What happened?
- Who are you?
- I'm her son.
- What happened?
- You can probably help us out inside.
We don't know what happened yet.
- Hop in the back of the ambulance.
- Step.
One more.
We got one more lift.
I'm getting
a little resistance here,
Michael.
Lift.
I'm right here.
Excuse me, sir.
Does your mother take
any medications?
- No.
- Excuse me,
- I couldn't hear you.
- No.
Sir, when was the last time
you spoke to her?
I don't know.
Mr. Fleck.
Sorry to bother you.
I'm detective garrity.
This is my partner,
detective Burke.
We had a few questions for
you, but you weren't home,
so we spoke with your mother.
Oh.
What did you say to her?
Did you do this?
What? No.
No, no, no. We just
asked her some questions,
and she got hysterical.
Hyperventilating,
collapsed and
hit her head pretty hard.