Yeah. The doctor said
she had a stroke.
We're sorry to hear about that.
But, like I said, I still have
some questions for you.
They're about
the subway killings
that happened last week.
You've heard about them, right?
Yeah.
It's horrible.
Right.
So, we spoke with your boss
over at haha's.
He said you were fired
for bringing a gun
into the children's hospital.
- Is that true, Mr. Fleck?
- It was a prop.
It's part of my act.
I'm a party clown.
All right.
So, why were you fired?
They said I wasn't funny enough.
Can you imagine that?
If you don't mind, I have to
go take care of my mother.
Your boss also
gave us one of your cards.
This condition of yours,
the laughing,
is it real,
or some sort of clown thing?
- A clown thing?
- Yeah.
I mean, is it part of your act?
What do you think?
It's exit only.
She's gonna be okay.
I'm gonna get a coffee.
You want one?
Yeah.
So, the other night,
I told my youngest son Billy,
you know, the new one,
the not-so-bright one.
I told him, "the garbage strike
is still going on, Billy."
And he says, and I'm
not kidding, Billy says,
"so, where are we gonna get
all our garbage from?"
And finally,
in a world where everyone
thinks they could do my job,
we got this video tape
from pogo's comedy club,
right here in Gotham.
Here's a guy who thinks
if you just keep laughing,
it'll somehow make you funny.
Check out this joker.
Oh, my god.
I hated school as a kid.
But my mother would always say,
"you should enjoy it.
One day, you'll have to
work for a living."
"No, I won't, ma.
I'm gonna be a comedian."
You shoulda listened
to your mother.
Hey, one more.
One more, Bobby.
All right, let's see one more.
I love this guy.
It's funny,
when I was a little boy
and told people
I was gonna be a comedian,
everyone laughed at me.
Well, no one's laughing now.
You can say that again, pal.
All right, we got a great show
for you tonight.
Chuck conby is here,
actress joanne mulligan,
and new music from
Mel rubin and the stiffs.
As tensions mount
around the Metro area,
mayor Stokes has pleaded
for cooler heads to prevail.
City services
have been affected,
and some businesses have decided
to remain closed
amid the unrest.
Chuck Stevens filed this report.
The anger and resentment
that's been building
in the city for weeks
seems close to exploding.
Protesters,
many dressed as clowns,
took to the streets today
in one of
several planned demonstrations
taking on the city's elite,
including a massive rally
outside
tomorrow night's
benefit at Wayne hall.
What's the point of all this?
- The rich.
- Thomas Wayne.
That's what this whole
thing is about.
The whole system.
Wayne,
who recently announced
he is running for mayor,
will be attending the benefit.
You might remember
it was Thomas Wayne
who first referred to
many of Gotham's residents
as "clowns."
Today, he offered little in
the way of an apology.
Well, what I will say is,
there's something wrong
with those people.
I am here to help them.
I'm gonna
lift them out of poverty,
help make their lives better.
That is why I'm running.
And they may not realize it,
but I'm their only hope.
Down with Wayne!
Can I help you, pal?
I don't know what to say.
Do you want an autograph
or something?
No.
My name is Arthur.
Penny fleck is my mother.
Jesus.
You're the guy that came to
my house yesterday.
Yes.
I'm sorry I just showed up.
But my mother
told me everything,
and I had to talk to you.
Look, pal, I'm not your father.
What's wrong with you?
Look at us.
I think you are.
Well, that's impossible
because you're adopted,
and I never slept with
your mother.
- I wasn't adopted.
- What do you want from me?
- Money?
- No, I don't...
I wasn't adopted.
Jesus. She never told you?
Told me what?
Your mother adopted you
while she was working for us.
That's not true.
Why are you saying that?
Then she was arrested
and committed
to arkham state hospital,
when you were just a little boy.
Why are you saying this?
I don't need you to
tell me lies.
I know it seems strange.
I don't mean to
make you uncomfortable.
I don't know
why everyone is so rude.
I don't know why you are.
I don't want anything from you.
Maybe a little bit of warmth,
maybe a hug, dad!
How about just a little bit
of fucking decency?
What is it with you people?
You say that stuff
about my mother.
She's crazy.
She's...
You think this is funny?
Dad, it's me. Come on.
Touch my son again,
I'll fucking kill you.
Hello, Mr. Fleck.
This is detective garrity.
We met the other night
at Gotham general.
My partner and I had a few
more questions for you.
We stopped by your apartment
today, but you weren't home.
Please give me a call
when you get this message.
Again, detective garrity,
and my number is 212... 99.
This message is
for Arthur fleck.
My name is Shirley woods.
I work on
the Murray Franklin show.
I don't know if you're aware,
but Murray played
a clip of your stand-up
on the show recently,
and we have gotten an amazing
response from our viewers.
Murray asked me to give you
a call and see if you're...
Who is this?
Oh, hi, this is Shirley woods.
I'm the show booker from
live with Murray Franklin.
Is this Arthur?
Yes.
Hi, Arthur.
Well, as I was saying,
we've gotten a lot of calls
about your clip.
Amazing responses.
And Murray asked
if I would reach out to you
to see if you would
come on as his guest.
Murray wants me
on the Murray Franklin show?
Yeah. Isn't that great?
He'd love to talk to you,
maybe do some of your act?
That sound good to you?
Yeah, that sounds great.
Can we set up a date right now?
Are you available next Thursday?
Hey.
Man,
I'm sorry about that, my man.
All records 10 years or older,
they store in the basement,
and you're talking about
something 30 years ago, so...
Can I ask you a question?
Sure.
How does someone
wind up in here?
Have they all, all the people
committed crimes?
Well, yeah, some have.
You know, some are just crazy.
Pose dangers to
themselves and others.
Some just got
nowhere else to go.
Don't know what to do, you know?
- Yeah. I hear you, brother.
- Hmm.
Sometimes,
I don't know what to do.
Last time, I ended up taking
it out on some people.
I thought it was gonna bother
me, but it really hasn't.
What's that?
I fucked up and
did some bad shit.
You know what I'm talking about,
it's so hard to just try and
be happy all the time.
Hey, listen, man.
I'm just
an administrative assistant.
Like a clerk, you know.
All I do is file paperwork.
I don't know what to tell you.
But you should see somebody.
You know, they got programs,
city services, stuff like that.
Oh, yeah.
They cut all those.
All right, here it is.
Fleck.
Penny fleck. Let's see.
Diagnosed by
Dr. Benjamin stoner.
Oh. "The patient suffers
from delusional psychosis
and narcissistic
personality disorder." Mmm.
"Was found guilty of endangering
the welfare
of her own child."
What?
You said she's your mother.
Uh...
I'm sorry, man. Like I said,
I can't release these records,
you know, without proper forms.
I could get in trouble.
Look, if you want to bring
your mom in here to sign,
that'll be much easier,
but I can't let this go
without her signature, okay?
I'm sorry.
No, man! Shit!
Come on, man. Give it...
Hey! Hey!
We went over this,
penny. You adopted him.
We have all the paperwork
right here.
That's not true.
Thomas had that all made up,
so it stayed our secret.
You also stood by
while one of your boyfriends
repeatedly abused
your adopted son
and battered you.
Penny,
your son was found tied
to a radiator
in your filthy apartment.
Malnourished with multiple
bruises across his body
and severe trauma to his head.
I never heard him cry.
He's always been
such a happy little boy.
It's time for bed.
Oh, my god!
What are you doing in here?
You're in the wrong apartment.
Your name's Arthur, right?
You live down the hall.
I really need you to leave.
My little girl is sleeping
in the other room.
Please.
I had a bad day.
Can I call someone?
Is your mother home?
Shut up!
Hey, penny.
Penny fleck.
I always hated that name.
You know how you used to tell me
that my laugh was a condition?
That there was
something wrong with me?
There isn't.
That's the real me.
Happy.
Happy. Hmm.
I haven't been happy
one minute of
my entire fucking life.
You know what's funny?
You know
what really makes me laugh?
I used to think
that my life was a tragedy...
But now I realize
it's a fucking comedy.
A very fine actor.
He's got a new movie
called American playboy
opening this week
across the country.
Will you please welcome
a good friend
of the show, Mr. Ethan chase.
Good to see you, Ethan.
You're looking great, Ethan.
Thank you very much.
You're looking good yourself.
Ah, can't complain.
Hey, Murray.
Thanks so much for having...
Thank you so much for
having me on the show.
It's been
a lifelong dream of mine.
I'm nervous right now.
- You are?
- I am nervous.
Hey, Murray. I've been on...
I'm sorry. What's that?
Oh, that's very funny, Murray.
You know, I'm also a comedian.
Would you like to hear a joke?
Yeah? All of you?
Okay.
Knock...
Knock, knock.
That's life
that's life
that's what all the people say
you're riding high in April
shot down in may
but I know I'm gonna change that tune
when I'm back on top
back on top in June
I said, that's life
that's life
and as funny as it may seem
some people get their kicks
stompin' on a dream
but I don't let it,
let it get me down
'cause this fine old world
it keeps spinnin' around
I've been a puppet, a pauper, a pirate
a poet, a pawn and a king
I've been up and down and over and out
and I know one thing
each time I find myself flat on my face
I pick myself up
and get back in the race
that's life
I tell ya, I can't deny it
I thought of quitting, baby
but my heart just ain't gonna buy it
and if I didn't think
it was worth one single try
coming.
I'd jump right on a big bird
and then I'd fly...
Hey, Arthur.
How's it going?
Oh, hey, guys.
Come on in.
Did you get a new gig?
No.
Oh, you must be going down to
that rally at city hall.
I hear it's gonna be nuts.
Oh, is that today?
Yeah.
What's with the makeup then?
My mom died.
I'm celebrating.
Right. We heard.
That's why we came by.
We figured, you know, you
could use some cheering up.
Aw, that's sweet.
But, no, I feel good.
Yeah, I stopped
taking my medication.
I feel a lot better now.
Oh, okay. Good for you.
So, hey, listen,
I don't know if you heard,
but the cops have been coming
around the shop,
talking to all the guys
about those subway murders.
- And, um...
- They didn't talk to me.
That's because the suspect
was a regular-sized person.
If it was a fucking midget,
you'd be in jail right now.
Anyway, um,
hoyt said
that they talked to you,
and now they're looking for me,