Hero - MoviesMod.Zip
The news never ends.
This is 1080 gcr.
You get all the news you need,
all day long.
Good morning.
It's 42 degrees at 10:30 on
this Thursday, October 15th.
I'm Stan I. Brooks,
and here's what's happening.
It's day 18
of the garbage strike,
with 10,000 tons of garbage
piling up every day.
Even the nicest sections
of the city
are looking like slums.
Health commissioner
Edward o'Rourke is
declaring a city-wide
state of emergency
for the first time in decades.
There's no need to
wait until somebody dies
or comes down
with typhoid fever.
It's already
a serious situation.
It's something that affects
almost everyone in the city,
no matter who they are
or where they live.
You can't go down
no one Avenue
without seeing nothing
but garbage and rats.
It's starting to
affect my business
when customers can't get in here
because of
the garbage situation.
I'm not out that long
to smell it,
but I think to look at it,
it's terrible.
It don't affect me except
for the very bad smell here.
It's horrific.
It's a mess.
I've been in this country
for 50 years,
and I've never seen
anything like it.
What is this world coming to?
Put 'em in a room,
let 'em sit there and talk
until they get it over with.
24 hours, 48 hours,
how long it takes.
The idea of
the national guard moving in
and cleaning up is a good idea.
In other news,
the building industry
and landlords today
expressed concern
over the latest
increase in heating oil prices.
Renters in the Metro area
are certain to feel the pinch...
Yo, what's up
with your shoes, bro?
Nice outfit, pal.
If you're gonna be
a clown, at least you could be
a good one.
You know that, right?
- Hey! Hey!
- Grab it!
Go, go, go!
Hey!
He's coming!
Come on, clown, let's go!
We've got the sign.
- Look at him running.
- Let's go!
Stop them!
Go, go, go, go!
Watch the car, watch the car!
Where's your sign,
clown?
Hey!
Go, clown! Come on!
Stop them!
Go! Come on!
Come on, run!
Hey!
You fucking...
Oh, shit! Good hit.
Come on!
Beat his ass up.
Come on! This guy's weak.
He can't do nothing.
Harder! Harder!
Beat him up. Take his stuff.
Let's go, let's go!
Come on. Let's go!
Ha!
Is it just me,
or is it getting crazier
out there?
- It is certainly tense.
- Hmm.
People are upset.
They're struggling.
Looking for work.
These are tough times.
How about you?
Have you been keeping up
with your journal?
Yes, ma'am.
Great.
Did you bring it with you?
Arthur.
Last time, I asked you
to bring your journal
with you for these appointments.
Can I see it?
I've been using it as a journal,
but also as a joke diary.
Funny thoughts or observations.
I think I told you
I'm pursuing a career
in stand-up comedy.
No, you didn't.
I think I did.
"I just hope my death makes
more sense than my life."
How does it feel to
have to come here?
Does it help to
have someone to talk to?
I think I felt better
when I was locked up
in the hospital.
And have you thought more about
why you were locked up?
Who knows?
I was wondering
if you could ask the doctor
to increase my medication.
Arthur, you're on
seven different medications.
Surely,
they must be doing something.
I just don't want to
feel so bad anymore.
Would you please
stop bothering my kid?
I wasn't bothering him.
I was...
Just stop.
What? You think that's funny?
I'm sorry. I have a...
I'm sorry.
Happy,
did you check the mail
before you came up?
Yeah, mom.
Nothing.
And finally, tonight,
just when you thought
it couldn't get any worse,
authorities are saying
the city is under siege
by scores of rats.
And not just any rats,
but super rats,
who are hard to kill.
He must not be
getting my letters.
Yeah.
It's Thomas Wayne, mom.
He's a busy man.
Please. I worked
for that family for years.
The least he could do
is write back.
Here.
Don't get all worked up. Eat.
You need to eat.
Look how skinny you are.
Both victims
were taken to Gotham general.
Sounds like
the city needs to
find the pied Piper.
He'll make a great mayor.
Everybody says so.
Oh, yeah. Everybody who?
Who do you talk to?
Well, everybody on the news.
He's the only one
who could save the city.
He owes it to us.
Come sit. It's starting.
Yay, Murray.
From
ncb studios in Gotham city,
it's live with Murray Franklin!
Tonight, Murray welcomes
Sandra winger...
Oh, Sandra winger's on.
And the piano stylings
of yeldon and Chantel.
Joining Murray, as always,
Ellis drane
and his jazz orchestra.
And now, without further ado,
Murray Franklin.
Thank you.
We got a great-looking
audience tonight.
Yeah!
Wow. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
So, everybody's heard
about the super rats that
- are in Gotham now, right?
- Yeah.
Well, today, the mayor said
he has a solution.
You ready for this?
Super cats.
But in all seriousness,
I mean, these rats are...
I love you, Murray!
I love you, too.
Hey, Bobby,
would you put the lights on?
Who is that?
Was that you?
You wanna stand up, please?
Stand up for me.
Go ahead.
What's your name?
Hi, Murray. Arthur.
- Arthur?
- My name's Arthur.
Oh, okay. Well, there's
something special about you,
Arthur, I could tell.
Where are you from?
I live right here in the city
with my mother.
Okay, hold on.
Hold on.
There's nothing funny
about that.
I lived with my mother before
I made it. Just me and her.
I'm that kid whose father went
out for a pack of cigarettes,
and he never came back.
Aww.
I know
what that's like, Murray.
I've been the man of the house
for as long as I can remember.
I take good care of my mother.
All that sacrifice,
she must love you very much.
She does.
She always tells me to smile
and put on a happy face.
She says I was put here
to spread joy and laughter.
Aww.
Wow.
I like that. I like that
a lot. Come on down.
Come on. For that,
you gotta come down.
Come on! Come on.
Come on.
Okay, we got a big show
tonight. Stay tuned.
We'll be right back.
That was great, Arthur.
Thank you.
I mean, I loved hearing
what you had to say.
It made my day.
Thanks, Murray.
You see all this,
the lights, the show,
the audience, all that stuff?
I'd give it all up
in a heartbeat
to have a kid like you.
- What's up, ladies?
- Hey, Randall. What's up?
Another day in chuckle town.
Yup.
You okay?
I heard about
the beatdown you took.
Fucking savages.
It was just a bunch of kids.
I should have left it alone.
No.
They'll take everything
from you if you do that.
All the crazy shit out there.
They're animals.
You know what?
Here.
What is it?
Take it.
It's for you.
You gotta
protect yourself out there.
Otherwise,
you're gonna get fucked.
Randall,
I'm not supposed to have a gun.
Don't sweat it, art.
No one has to know.
And you can pay me back
some other time.
You know you're my boy.
Arthur,
hoyt wants to
see you in his office.
Hey, Gary. You know
what I've always wondered?
No idea.
Do you people call it
miniature golf
or is it just golf to you?
Punch him in the dick,
Gary.
Hello, hoyt.
Gary said you wanted to see me.
How's the comedy career?
Are you a famous stand-up yet?
Not quite.
Just been
working on my material.
No, don't sit.
This'll be quick.
Look, I like you, Arthur.
You know, a lot of the guys,
they think you're a freak,
but I like you.
I don't even know
why I like you.
But I got another complaint.
It's starting to piss me off.
Kenny's music.
The guy said you disappeared.
Never even returned his sign.
Because I got jumped.
Didn't you hear?
For a sign?
That's bullshit.
It doesn't even make sense.
Just get him his sign back.
He's going out of business,
for god's sake, Arthur.
Why would I keep his sign?
How the fuck do I know?
Why does anybody do anything?
If you don't return the sign,
I gotta take it
out of your paycheck.
Are we clear?
Listen, I'm trying to help you.
Okay? And I'll tell you
something else.
The other guys,
they don't feel comfortable
around you, Arthur,
because people
think you're weird.
Okay? And I can't
have that around me.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait.
Thank you.
This building is so awful,
isn't it?
right, mommy?
Yes, we can hear you, gigi.
It's so awful, mommy.
Right, mommy?
- Good night.
- This building's
- so awful, isn't it?
- Mmm-hmm.
Hey.
Come on.
The moon is a silver dollar
shining up in the sky
that's the dream we can buy...
- Look up.
- Mmm.
Maybe the mailman's
throwing them away.
Mom, why are these letters
so important to you?
What do you think he's gonna do?
He's gonna help us.
But you worked for him,
what, 30 years ago?
Why would he help us?
Because Thomas Wayne
is a good man.
If he knew how we were living,
if he saw this place,
it would make him sick.
I can't explain it to you
any better than that.
I don't want you worrying
about money, mom.
Or me.
Everybody's telling me
that my stand-up's
ready for the big clubs.
But, happy, what makes you
think you could do that?
- What do you mean?
- I mean...
Don't you have to be funny
to be a comedian?
Zoom, zoom, zoom, zoom
the world is in a mess
with politics and taxes
and people grinding axes
there's no happiness
happiness is not a riddle
when I'm listening to that
big bass fiddle
Slap that bass
slap it till its dizzy
slap that bass
keep the rhythm busy
zoom, zoom, zoom
misery, you've got to go...
Hey, what's your name?
Arthur.
Hey, Arthur,
you're a really good dancer.
I know.
You know who's not?
Him.
Happy, what was that?
Are you okay?
Mom, what?
That noise!
Did you hear that noise?
I'm watching an old war movie!
Turn it down!
Um...
Sorry, mom.
You good?
It's nice to see these couples
out at my show.
I have a wife.
We love to role-play.
- Ooh!
- Yes, yes, very sexy.
My favorite one right now is
professor and senior
who really needs
to pass my class to graduate.
Yes.
So, I'll tell you how I operate.
I'm a professor at
a prestigious
new england university...
And my wife is a senior
in my "intro to western civ."
I know. I know.
Why is she a senior in the
intro? I didn't buy it either.
So, she comes to me
during my office hours.
It's Monday and Wednesday,
three to five.
She says,
"excuse me, professor Lewis."
I can't use my real last name
at this college
'cause they don't hire Jews.
It's something I'll address
once I have tenure,
but for now...
She says,
"excuse me, professor Lewis,
I think I might be
in danger of failing
your 'intro to western civ, '
and I just want you to know
I'm willing to do
anything to pass."
And I said, "anything?"
And she said...
- Oh, hey.
- Hey.
Were you following me today?
Yeah.
I thought that was you.
I was hoping you'd come in
and Rob the place.