and I just wanna know
what you said.
Make sure our stories line up.
- Seeing as how you're my boy.
- Yeah, that's important.
- That makes a lot of sense.
- You know what I mean?
Thank you, Randall.
Thank you so much.
Arthur!
No!
What?
Why would you do that, Arthur?
Do you watch
the Murray Franklin show?
Yeah.
I'm gonna be on tonight.
It fucking crazy, innit?
Me on the telly.
What the fuck, Arthur?
What?
It's okay, Gary.
You can go.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Oh!
Don't look. Just go.
Fuck.
Hey, Arthur?
Yeah?
Arthur, can you get the lock?
Shit.
Sorry, Gary.
Gary?
Yeah.
You were the only one
that was ever nice to me.
Skedaddle.
Hey, Arthur!
We need to talk.
Oh!
Hey! Stop, Arthur!
Arthur!
Watch it!
Out of the way!
Move!
Arthur!
Shit.
Hey! Hey!
Arthur, stop!
Go! Go!
Now
departing, o-train, downtown.
Stand clear of
the closing doors.
Hold that train! Hold it!
Get out! Get outta here!
Next stop, bedford park.
Masks off!
Get your mask off!
Signs down! Now!
Police! Signs down!
Signs down.
What the fuck!
Beat his ass!
Stop fighting! Police!
Police! Get down!
Get down! Get the fuck back!
Police! Get down.
Get the fuck down!
Stay the fuck back! Down!
What the...
Arthur!
Burke!
Don't do it!
Two officers on the train
were violently confronted
by the crowd,
and tonight are in serious
but stable condition
at Gotham metropolitan.
We're going live now to
co-anchor Courtney weathers,
who's standing by outside
the bedford park station,
near where the shooting
took place.
Courtney,
what's the scene there?
Murray.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's Mr. Franklin, buddy.
Oh, come on, gene.
That's all bullshit.
Thank you, Murray.
I feel like I know you.
I've been watching you forever.
Thank you.
What's with the face?
I mean,
are you part of the protest?
No.
No, I don't believe
in any of that.
I don't believe in anything.
I just thought
it'd be good for my act.
For your act? Didn't you hear
what happened on the subway?
Some clown got killed.
He's aware of that.
He's aware of that. Yeah.
No, I hadn't heard.
- Yeah.
- You see?
This is what I'm telling you.
The audience is gonna go crazy
if you put this guy on.
Maybe for a bit,
but not a whole segment.
Gene, it's gonna work.
It's gonna work.
We're gonna go with it.
Thank you, Murray.
Couple rules, though.
No cursing.
No off-color material.
We do a clean show.
- Okay?
- Mmm-hmm.
You'll go on
right after Dr. Sally.
I love Dr. Sally.
Good, good. Someone will
- come and get you, okay?
- Okay. Perfect.
Good luck.
- Thanks, Murray.
- Okay.
- Murray, one small thing.
- Yeah.
When you bring me out,
can you introduce me as joker?
What's wrong
with your real name?
That's what you called me
on the show.
A joker.
Do you remember?
- Did I?
- I don't know.
Well, if you say so, kid,
you know, joker it is.
It's good.
Thanks, Murray.
I'll try it, you know,
but I'm not sure
my wife will let me do it.
Maybe my next wife.
You gotta see
our next guest for yourself.
I'm pretty sure
this guy could use a doctor.
Oh!
Does he have sexual problems?
Oh, he looks like
he's got a lot of problems.
All right, Bobby, let's show
that clip one last time.
I hated school as a kid.
But my mother would always say,
"you should enjoy it.
One day, you'll have to
work for a living."
"No, I won't, ma.
I'm gonna be a comedian."
Okay. You may...
You may have seen that clip
of our next guest.
Now, before he comes out,
I just want to say
that we're all heartbroken
about what's going on
in the city tonight.
But this is
how he wanted to come out,
and honestly, I think
we could all use a good laugh.
So, please welcome, joker.
Are you all right, doctor?
Well,
that was quite an entrance.
You okay?
Yeah.
This is exactly
how I imagined it.
Well, that makes one of us.
So, can you tell us
about this look?
When we spoke earlier,
you mentioned that this look
is not a political statement.
Is that right?
That's right, Murray.
I'm not political.
I'm just trying to
make people laugh.
And how's that going for you?
So, I know you're a comedian.
You been working on
any new material?
You wanna tell us a joke?
Yeah?
Okay.
He's got a book.
A book of jokes.
Take your time.
We got all night.
Okay, okay. Here's one.
Knock, knock.
And you had to look that up?
I want to get it right.
Knock, knock.
Who's there?
It's the police, ma'am.
Your son's been hit
by a drunk driver.
He's dead.
Oh, no, no, no.
No, you cannot joke about that.
Yeah, that's not funny, Arthur.
That's not the kind of humor
we do on this show.
Okay. I'm... yeah, I'm sorry.
It's just, you know, it's been
a rough few weeks, Murray.
Ever since
I killed
those three wall street guys.
Okay, I'm waiting
for the punchline.
There is no punchline.
It's not a joke.
You're serious, aren't you?
You're telling us you killed
those three young men
on the subway?
Mmm-hmm.
And why should we believe you?
I got nothing left to lose.
Nothing can hurt me anymore.
My life is nothing but a comedy.
Well, let me get this straight,
you think that killing
those guys is funny?
I do.
And I'm tired
of pretending it's not.
Comedy is subjective, Murray.
Isn't that what they say?
All of you,
the system that knows so much,
you decide
what's right or wrong.
The same way that you decide
what's funny or not!
Get him off!
Well, okay,
I think I might understand
that you did this to
start a movement,
to become a symbol?
Come on, Murray.
Do I look like the kind of clown
that could start a movement?
I killed those guys
because they were awful.
Everybody is awful these days.
It's enough to
make anyone crazy.
Okay. So, that's it,
you're crazy.
That's your defense
for killing three young men?
No.
They couldn't carry a tune
to save their lives.
Oh, why is everybody
so upset about these guys?
If it was me
dying on the sidewalk,
you'd walk right over me!
I pass you every day,
and you don't notice me.
But these guys, what,
because Thomas Wayne
went and cried about them on TV?
You have a problem
with Thomas Wayne, too?
Yes, I do.
Have you seen what it's like
out there, Murray?
Do you ever actually
leave the studio?
Everybody just yells
and screams at each other.
Nobody's civil anymore.
Nobody thinks what it's like
to be the other guy.
You think men like
Thomas Wayne ever think
what it's like to be
someone like me?
To be somebody but themselves?
They don't.
They think that
we'll just sit there
and take it,
like good little boys!
That we won't werewolf
and go wild!
You finished?
I mean, it's so much
self-pity, Arthur.
You sound like
you're making excuses
for killing those young men.
Not everybody,
and I'll tell you this,
not everyone is awful.
You're awful, Murray.
Me? I'm awful?
Oh, yeah, how am I awful?
Playing my video.
Inviting me on this show.
You just wanted to
make fun of me.
You're just like
the rest of them.
You don't know
the first thing about me, pal.
Look what happened, because of
what you did. What it led to.
There are riots out there.
Two policemen are
in critical condition,
and you're laughing.
You're laughing.
Someone was killed today,
because of what you did.
I know.
How about another joke, Murray?
No, I think we've had
enough of your jokes.
- What do you get...
- I don't think so.
When you cross
a mentally-ill loner
with a society that abandons him
and treats him like trash?
Call the police, gene!
- I'll tell you what you get!
- Call the police.
You get
what you fucking deserve!
Good night.
And always remember, that's...
Breaking news.
Popular TV talk show host,
Murray Franklin
was shot dead tonight on the
live telecast of his program.
The man who was
introduced by Franklin
as "joker" is
currently under arrest.
Police led the suspect
handcuffed out of the studio.
Merely just a punchline
to a joke...
You get what you
deserve!
Looting and rioting
have intensified here...
...rioting
throughout the city.
...with a society
that abandons him
and treats him like trash?
This mob of clowns...
Many wearing clown masks.
If it was me
dying on the sidewalk,
- you'd walk right over me.
- To all of
those who have been
ignored by the system.
And always remember,
that's life!
And as you see,
Gotham is burning.
In the white room
with black curtains near the station
black roof country, no gold pavements
tired starlings
silver horses ran down moonbeams
in your dark eyes
dawnlight smiles on you leaving
my contentment
I'll wait in this place
where the sun never shines
wait in this place
where the shadows run from themselves
stop laughing,
you freak! This isn't funny.
Yeah, the whole
fucking city's on fire
'cause of what you did.
All units,
fire reported, north of alley.
Code four for medical.
I know.
Isn't it beautiful?
Go over there.
Hey, Wayne.
You get
what you fucking deserve.
No! Pal!
Come on, get up!
Come on, man, get up.
What's so funny?
Just thinking of a joke.
Do you want to tell it to me?
You wouldn't get it.
That's life
that's life
and as funny as it may seem
some people get their kicks
stompin' on a dream
but I don't let it,
let it get me down
'cause this fine old world
it keeps spinnin' around
I've been a puppet, a pauper, a pirate
a poet, a pawn and a king
I've been up and down and over and out
and I know one thing
each time I find myself flat on my face
I pick myself up
and get back in the race
that's life
and I can't deny it
many times I thought of cuttin' out
but my heart won't buy it
but if there's nothing shakin'
come here this July
I'm gonna roll myself up in a big ball
and die
my, my
Isn't it rich?
Are we a pair?
Me here at last on the ground
you in mid-air
send in the clowns
Isn't it bliss?
Don't you approve?
One who keeps tearing around
one who can't move
where are the clowns?
Send in the clowns
just when I stopped
opening doors
finally knowing
the one that I wanted was yours
making my entrance again
with my usual flair
sure of my lines
no one is there
Don't you love farce?
My fault, I fear
I thought that you'd want what I want
sorry, my dear
but where are the clowns?
There ought to be clowns
well, maybe next year
Hero - MoviesMod.Zip